softarea51.com 2013-06-09

# Privacy & Policy

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive that keep track of your online patterns and preferences in order to enhance your browsing experience. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information (name, address, email address, or telephone number) while on our site. 

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Google Advertising Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that "SoftArea51.com" is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
